Paweł Kanarek

Mobile Developer with over 10 years of commercial experience specialized in Xamarin and .NET MAUI multi-platform frameworks. As a Machine Learning enthusiast who spent the past year in self-study, I believe that I would be a great asset to your AI Engineering team.

Experience

Self Employed

Al Developer Aug 2023 - Present

- Fine-tuned the Stable Diffusion XL (SDXL) model to generate animated sprites.
- Collected, prepared, and created a dataset consisting of 560 labeled images.
- Created a training script for the SDXL model in the Flax framework. See my spraix repository for more details.
- Completed PyTorch for Deep Learning Bootcamp on Udemy and Andrej Karpathy's course Neural Networks: Zero to Hero.

Legimi

Xamarin Developer Aug 2022 – Aug 2023

- Maintained popular Legimi application on Android, iOS, Windows, MacOS and e-Ink platforms.
- Wrote documentation, planned, estimated, and implemented new features.
- Managed multitasking during two-week tech support sprints including user and internal teams assistance, bug fixes, CI pipelines management, and multi-platform releases.
- Created automated UI, integration, and unit tests.
- Gained experience in C# functional programming using Reactive Extensions.

Insys Video Technologies

Mobile Technical Leader July 2020 - July 2022

Senior Xamarin Developer | Apr 2020 - July 2020

Xamarin Developer June 2016 - Apr 2020

Solar2D Game and App Developer | Aug 2013 - June 2016

- Performed technical interviews in the hiring process.
- Created streaming applications for watching DRM-protected live streams and VODs for iOS, Android, AndroidTV, AppleTV, Windows Phone platforms with Xamarin and Solar2D frameworks.
- · Collaborated in creating custom Framework and White Label Product, leading to dozens of successful implementations; examples include: simpliTV Android / iOS / AndroidTV, PAOK TV Android / iOS, BeActiveTV Android / iOS, INEA Online TV Android / iOS, Cineman Android / iOS, Mojeekino.pl Android / iOS, Benfica Play Android / iOS, Trwam TV Android / iOS.
- Set up infrastructure for UI and integration tests.

Technologies

Listed by proficiency; enthusiastic about the bolded ones.

- Programming Languages: **C#**, **Python**, **Kotlin**, Java, Lua, **GDScript**, Dart, JavaScript, Objective-C, C++, C, Assembly, F#.
- Frameworks: Xamarin, MAUI, **PyTorch**, **Jax**, **Flax**, Flutter, ASP.NET, **Godot**, Solar2D.
- IDEs: **JetBrains Rider**, **VS Code**, **Visual Studio** (where I have published extension on the Marketplace), Android Studio, XCode.
- Other: git, Jenkins, GitHub, Hugging Face, Stable Diffusion, Rx.NET, RealmDB, Jira, Redmine, ExoPlayer, MVVMCross, Prism.

Education

Poznań University of Technology

B.Sc. in Automatic Control and Robotics 2011 - 2017

• For my diploma thesis, "Weather Station on the Arduino Processor", I developed a web app in ASP.NET and created mobile apps for Android and iOS platforms, with real-time view of the results from the station.

Languages

Polish: Native speaker.

• English: Fluent (B2 level).